Don't tell anyone about yesterday.
What's that? Are you alone?
I feel like a new employee.
Pressure.
You'll get a letter.
Oh, hey.
It's okay. It's okay.
I'm fine.
Okay, let's see.
I'll go.
What the hell?
That's so good.
Thank you for your hard work.
Hello, everyone. This is Yuki Yoda and
I'm Yuki Yoda and Junmiku Uchino from Nogizaka 46.
And since this is our collaboration month, we'd like to invite a wonderful guest.
Please join us.
Thank you very much.
I'm Ayaka.
I'm Bunta.
Sanno Gai.
Barrier Talks.
Pleased to meet you.
That's great. We want one too.
I'll let the non-idol guy say hello.
I'm jealous.
Sanno is in the group and they're in Fukuoka.
That's what they say, isn't it?
I'm glad.
I'm often asked what I mean by that by the audience.
Like, "What do you mean?
It just came to me.
Sannou-gai.
Sanno Gai.
Like, "Issei nose"?
Yes, yes, yes.
That's also a dialect.
I just found out.
What?
I didn't know it was a dialect.
I didn't know that.
It was shown yesterday.
I went to Tokyo.
That's true.
I'm still not sure how I feel about it.
I often say "tidy up" and "fix" but...
I don't think there's a dialect for it.
Hark.
Oh, I see.
Hark? Hark.
I ran an errand.
What? I used you.
You used Hark.
Rare.
We're all in Fukuoka today.
It's been a long time.
For those of you who don't know us, let me tell you something.
We usually make short dramas using Fukuoka dialect, and we post them on youtube and tiktok.
We post them on youtube and tiktok.
That's right.
I heard that you two are going to be in the show today.
Really?
I'm so happy!
Really? Really?
Which one was that?
He's running away.
I'm a little nervous.
By the way, have you seen the video?
Yesterday.
I was busy moving yesterday.
I just moved to Tokyo.
I'm glad.
Sorry, it's on paper.
On paper.
I was told to bring data.
If it's data, we can all put our tablets in.
Thank you very much.
And now, if you'll look behind me, you'll see my office today.
Oh, my God, when did this happen?
I can tell by the two of you... and your outfits.
Have either of you ever worked for a company before?
No.
No, but I worked at an inn.
That's very hot.
I've never worked there.
That's amazing.
Today, I'd like to capture their office worker side and Ayaka Fukuoka's daily life as an office worker at this company.
Yes, please.
So, first of all, may I have a quick look at myself?
There's a chance you won't want to do it.
There's also the possibility that you don't want to do it.
That's true.
It's very graphic.
In a good way.
Real.
How do you think about this?
I take a certain kind of man-woman thing, and I make a preamble from it, and I do that in Hakata.
Yes, yes, yes.
For example, most of the videos end with a promise to go out for dinner.
After that, you know...
After that, it's up to your imagination.
That's fine too.
It's not particularly gimmicky.
It's a video that you can't see all the way through.
It's a little hazy.
It's tantalizing.
By the way, do you usually act in plays?
I'm in a musical now.
What?
It's almost like it's my first time.
First time?
I've never done anything realistic like this.
I see... on the contrary.
A new side to you.
I'm looking forward to it.
Let's see your face on the tape.
Okay, who wants to go first?
Certainly.
I don't care where we start.
What do you want to do? First.
Let's start with you.
Or me first?
Miku, let's start with you.
Senpai, please.
Please, please, please, please.
Okay, Yanagida-san, solo first.
Okay.
Okay, I'll take some pictures.
First of all, this elevator hall.
Yes, sir.
And here's what the script says.
Mr. Yanagida is coming to work today.
He'll take the elevator first.
He's coming to work.
And I had to go out for a while.
I had to go out for a while, and I bumped into Mr. Yanagida.
Bumped into him?
You're a little hungover.
A little hungover.
Did you feel all right last night? I asked.
I was fine, but my head still feels a little off.
Like, "Well, it's no one's fault what happened yesterday.
Yes, sir.
I tell him.
I see.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Senpai, everyone!
Seniors.
Wow.
I'm a senior.
I'll just cushion you for a second.
I'll just take a little detour.
That's right.
Seniors are...
Big deal.
Let's do a quick flow.
Let's try a light flow, shall we?
Okay.
Then we'll watch.
It's a little warm.
I really want to go on a drama shoot like this.
No, but I'm super curious.
I made a mistake today and went to make hangover pills.
Yeah.
Hangover.
I made a mistake.
I took three more pills to make the pills.
I forgot.
I hate this.
Me too.
Yes, you may ask.
You said I could ask about your real age.
I'm 20.
Yes.
The last time we did this...
I was 23.
Yeah, you look older.
Really?
I knew it. Your face.
I don't know if you've noticed, but your face...
You don't look mature.
You look so mature.
I'm so glad.
I've heard that you're smaller when you stand up.
You're small when you stand up.
That's what Sona said.
That's right, that's right.
That's true.
When you sit down...
That's how small you are when you're sitting down.
When I stand up, she says I'm small.
You know...
I'm the same way.
First, you come out here, and then you go there with your hand.
I'll come to you from over here like this.
You're looking at the camera?
That's right.
That's your point, Mr. Ishimatsu.
Please look at this lens only.
Talking to the lens...
You never look at Bunta's face, do you?
Not even once.
It's like you're talking to the audience.
That's realistic.
I'm glad.
Hold the camera.
I'll just do a quick read.
Elevator's open.
Good morning, sir.
Morning. - Morning.
You okay last night?
I drank too much last night.
Did you have a good day?
Let's do it again today.
Thank you very much.
Oh, my God.
It's just the camera.
That's how many times it's been played.
It's perfect.
It's a little embarrassing.
Oh, my God.
A little bit.
I don't know, I don't see anyone else.
Super.
It's like I'm a posthumous elite, but I'm not.
Even though you're really a piece of shit
No, no, no, it's perfect.
It's so, so, so good.
Was it okay?
Let's do it like that.
Camera sound.
Okay, let's try it one time.
And the moment it closes, open it, push it, and it comes out.
Wait a minute, one at a time, the moment it closes.
I'll get it.
Okay, okay.
It's OK, it's OK, it's OK, it's OK, it's OK, it's OK, it's OK, it's OK.
I have to play a role at the moment it closes.
I'm thinking... my hands are light blue.
Quiet, seniors. Let's go.
Good morning. You were fine yesterday.
I was fine yesterday, but I still had a headache.
Wait a minute. Did I make a mistake?
Don't be nervous.
He's embarrassed by a beautiful woman. He's embarrassed by a beautiful woman.
Who's not usually pretty? Who's usually nervous?
I'll take the elevator. I'm nervous when it closes.
I'm off. Have a good day.
Good morning!
You okay last night?
You drank too much last night.
I was fine, sir.
Thank you very much.
I'm fine!
I saw your face for a second!
I'm OK!
Let's check it out.
Oh, I'm so embarrassed.
Oh, my God.
Good morning!
That princess is different.
It's a little thin, don't you think?
Don't do that.
She's so sweet!
What? ! What was that?
It's so good!
What do you think? Ippatsu-san.
It's great!
It's wonderful!
I was a little nervous.
But you speak in Hakata dialect.
It was easy to do.
I used my own words.
And the eye line.
The fact that you are so small when you stand up makes you look alive.
It's great!
It's so easy to stop and use your own words.
It's really good.
You're so bossy, but you're looking up at me.
There's a gap.
From an uncle's point of view...
I want to play BikTok with you.
I just found out.
I can't believe I just found out about this! That was so great!
No, no, no, no, no...
Here's what we're doing today.
Thank you for being the top hitter!
Thank you very much!
Next is Kazumatsu-san!
But you can sing too.
Musical style!
It's the actor's color!
Metoken
Yes, sir.
And while we were filming...
I'm going to have a senior come over.
If you'd like.
I'm sure you can get through to Ayaka without her knowing.
It's like a way to get through to Ayaka without her knowing.
That god cup.
As a fan gift
He's gonna be super excited.
Too many uncles!
Next time...
I'll get it.
Be cool. I'll just go over the lines.
Okay.
Okay, let's go.
Good work, sir.
Good work.
I made coffee. Would you like some?
Thank you, Miki.
Thank you.
Bon appétit.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'll check it out.
You're going a little overboard.
I'm smiling.
It's nice to be recognized like this.
Including you, Mr. Yada.
It's just a test.
I'll give you feedback.
Let's check it out.
We're happy, aren't we?
Hey, Mister...
It's perfect.
That's great.
It's so cute!
Can I see it the moment Ayaka disappears from sight?
The last one.
I'll watch too.
Don't look.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm fine.
Let's try it once.
Yes, sir.
Here we go.
Good work.
Thank you.
I made coffee. I'll drink it if you want.
Oh, wow! Thank you.
Wow, thank you so much.
Bon appétit.
Yes, thank you!
It's ok it's ok
It's so good!
Let's just check one more time.
Oh, I didn't look at the camera.
Oh, message.
I was looking at the guy, sorry.
Let's just go one more time.
Oh, yeah, sure.
I'll forget about it.
Don't look.
It's all right.
Let's just go one more time.
Yay, I can watch it again.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Samoa, it's as if it's been there all along.
I'm trying to make it disappear like a plant.
It's too good.
I'll try one last time.
Please.
Yes, please.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I made you some coffee. I'll drink it if you want.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you
Yes, OK
Yes, it's okay.
How's it going?
Thank you very much.
You look nice.
I have one more for you.
Last one for the office.
The last one.
This time, she's working hard.
Working.
And lastly, I'm whispering here.
He's interviewing.
It sure feels like a new hire.
Freshers.
Senpai will be there too.
Oh, my God, look at the back.
She looks great.
A little longer, Miku!
It's hard to see you over here, but...
Keep your eyes on the camera.
Just like that.
I can't eat it, it's too cute.
Look at me!
Please bear with me.
I'll do it.
What did I tell you?
You're the one!
Here we go!
Thank you for all your hard work.
Finally, the week is over.
What are you and your senpai doing tomorrow?
I haven't decided yet.
Are you alone?
No, I'm fine.
Oh, okay.
Just a minute.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
Meeting
A meeting.
I want to go with you.
He's fast.
If you can keep up with him...
I'd be happy to.
Oh...
Oh, by the way...
Yoda's not here.
I didn't see Yoda.
I don't know where she is.
Where's Yoda?
Fire extinguisher.
I got the extinguisher.
Food for all!
Oh, my God!
Thank you for your hard work.
Good job, guys.
It's over, isn't it?
What are you doing on your day off tomorrow?
Thank you.
See you later, Lion.
A ticket home.
Okay, okay.
I'm not very good at saying thank you.
I don't know how to say it.
Thank you.
Not at all!
Small or medium?
Underlay?
It's cute!
What?
It's so cute!
Isn't she great?
You're a great actor, too.
My lines are great!
I realized how great I was when I did it.
I've never done anything like it before.
Without my lines, I'm just me.
They each have their own good qualities.
I was so cute and sexy.
Sexuality.
Good job, sir.
Good work! Finally, this week is over.
It is, isn't it?
OK!
So cute!
It's great!
It's so cute! Amazing!
Okay, that's it.
That's all for now.
We're done shooting in the office.
How was it?
Were we okay?
We were not okay.
On the contrary, it was not good.
It wasn't good?
Around the circle?
The red tongue said you were cute.
I thought she was.
We thought so, too.
It's so cute!
I thought the same thing.
I thought it was cute.
I wasn't sure if I could do it.
But when I tried it...
No, it's so cute!
Even when I saw it live
It was so cute to see it live.
I'm looking forward to seeing the video
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm really looking forward to presenting it to you.
I'm looking forward to it.
How did it feel?
It feels safe, like home.
It is, isn't it?
My mom and dad.
It felt safe, like home.
And it was a little bit relaxing.
I enjoyed it.
It was great.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to show you the second half of the video after this.
The second half of the video will be posted on the account of Mr. Tonkotsu.
Please check it out too!
Please take a look.
Please do.
Also?
Channel
High rating
Please subscribe and rate our channel!
Please do.
No "bye-bye" or anything like that.
I don't like the language.
The Nogizaka way...
Just tell them I said hi.
Please say bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
See you later.
Thank you for watching.